# HA GIA TAN

#### SOFTWARE ENGINEER



# Introduction

I am a Software Engineer with 4 years of experience in web development. At 25, I have worked on a wide range of projects, from simple applications to complex systems, primarily using ReactJS, NextJS, JavaScript, TypeScript. I am confident in optimizing user experience, ensuring responsiveness and performance of websites, and always ready to learn new technologies to meet the requirements of each project.

For me, the important things of a frontend developer is attention to detail, write simplified code and scaling thinking. My goal is to become a good Front end developer. Provide users with quality products.

### **Work experience**

### Titan Technology Corporation (09/2021 - Now)

Titan Technology Corporation is a software technology company in Vietnam with around 200 employees. Although primarily an outsourcing company, its projects involve large-scale, high-profile ventures that are widely used worldwide, such as Mindgeek and Levvia (a product of Deloitte).

I currently work as a mid-level front-end developer on the Levuia project—an auditing platform for Deloitte. My daily tasks include progress reporting, functional analysis, and UI coding.

I use React (Redux, Hook, UI Library), JavaScript, Azure, and Slack to develop the product.

I'm now seeking a new opportunity that offers exposure to a wider range of projects and cutting-edge technologies.

### GenesisLabs - U.S (3/2021 - 06/2022)

GenesisLabs U.S. is a health and science company based in the U.S., specializing in research and experimentation. At this company, I work directly with the project manager.

I'm a junior-level front-end developer on the project, working as a freelancer after being hired through LinkedIn. My daily responsibilities include progress reporting, functional analysis, UI development, and unit testing, with an average commitment of 4 hours each evening.

I utilize NextJS, TypeScript, Docker, and Jira to develop the product.

This was my first job as a developer, and after over a year on the project, I've gained many valuable lessons.

### **Professional experience**

### Auvenir - Deloitte (09/2021 - Now)

A cloud-based, user-friendly quality management system tailor-made for forward-thinking accounting firms. QMG Cloud, with its modern interface, caters to all firm sizes. It integrates requirements from the Canadian Standards on Quality Management (CSQM) 1 and 2, as well as the Canadian Auditing Standards 22O.

Technologies used: React, Hook, Class, Redux, Semantic UI, Chart JS, Javascript.

Team size: 200+ members.

Position: Frontend developer

#### Responsibilities:

- Resolving application bugs based on customer's requirements, ensuring the stability and quality of the product.
- Collaborating closely with team members on defining and improving workflow processes.
- Reviewing the code of teammates and assisting newcomers.
- Defining and refining workflow processes to reduce performance-related bugs and enhance team-work efficiency.

### **LabMaster (O3/2O21 - Now)**

Project offers detailed insights into diseases and cellular discoveries made by scientists.

Technologies used: NextJS, NextAuth, Docker, Redux, MaterialUI, ChartJS, Typescript.

Team size: 4 members.

Position: Full-stack developer

### Responsibilities:

- Develop the UI for the system based on designs provided from Figma files.
- Develop the necessary features for a web-based information platform.
- · Write unit tests for the frontend files.
- Collaborate with the backend team to resolve server-related issues.
- Build and develop API, Database integration
- Building an authentication and authorization system, Performing testing and debugging, Deploying and managing servers, Implementing CI/CD, Interacting with external services

### Milano (06/2021 - 08/2021)

This is a project by the famous coffee brand Milano.

Technologies used: HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, Flickity JS, Responsive Web Design.

Team size: 1 member.

Position: Frontend developer

#### Responsibilities:

- Develop the UI for the system based on designs provided from Figma files.
- Design a user interface that adapts to all screen sizes.
- Optimize the website's performance.

### **Skills**

### **Programming Languages**

Javascript, TypeScript

I'm quite confident that I can catch up with other languages when needed very fast.

### **Web Front-end Technologies**

React, Redux, Next, Context API, Zustand, Angular, HTML5, CSS3, Shacdn UI, Ant Design, TailwindCSS, SASS, Vite. (I haven't used Angular for a while)

### Web Back-end Technologies

Frameworks/Libraries: Node.js, Express.js

Databases: MongoDB, Firebase

Cloud Services: Azure, Vercel, AWS (SES, S3)

### **Dev Tools**

Qit, Docker, Qithub, Qitlab, Jira, Figma, US Code, Slack, Postman, SourceTree, Redux Dev Tool.

### **Another Skills**

RESTful API, GraphQL

### Languages

### English

Read and understand specialized documents, communication skills.

#### **Vietnamese**

Native speaker.

# **Education**

Ho Chi Minh University of Foreign Languages Information Technology | 2017 - 2021

Major: Software Engineering

# **Contact Information**

**Q** 0987 150 799

District 1, Ho Chi Minh City

https://www.linkedin.com/in/giatan1507/

Thank you for viewing! ...
Looking Forward to hearing From you ... - Ha Gia Tan